clothes2order.ie 2017-04-09

# Privacy Policy - Clothes2order suppliers of Promotional Clothing, Uniforms, embroidered polo shirts and printed T-shirts.

## Privacy Policy

At Clothes2order.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We want you to be able to place your order with us free from worry and have strict privacy measures to ensure this is the case. "We" means Clothes2order.com, a site run by Quayside Clothing Ltd. [Click here for our full company details](https://www.clothes2order.ie/contact.php).

#### Personal information required to process your order

In order to process any order, we require your details including your name, billing address, delivery address, telephone number and email address. Your email address is required as a means of identification to allow you to access order placement area of the site and so that you can be updated with the progress of your order. Your phone number is only used to contact you if there is an issue with your order. All data is securely stored on our systems and is never distributed to any third parties.

#### Use of your personal information for marketing

You will only be sent marketing emails if you "opt in" to our email offers list when placing your order, or at a later point. Every marketing email we send contains an unsubscribe link allowing you to instantly remove your email address from future campaigns.

#### Security of your information

Clothes2order.com is fully PCI compliant and is assessed regularly by an independent PCI compliance scanning vendor, Security Metrics. No payment data (such as credit or debit card numbers) is stored on our systems. Entering of your personal data during the checkout process is protected by a GeoTrust SSL certificate. All personal data is handled with the upmost care and is never distributed to any third parties.

#### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive, and are often essential for the functionality of modern websites, including Clothes2order.com. Cookies can be deleted from your hard drive if you wish. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your browser settings to prevent that. Please note that if you choose not to accept cookies, you will not be able to place orders using our service. We regularly audit the cookies used by our system in order to keep these to a minimum. Please note that third party systems integrated with our site may also drop cookies; you should consult the privacy policy of those systems for more information. A full breakdown of cookies used by our site is shown below:

Cookie Title | Cookie File(s) | Essential? | Description | Intrusiveness | More Information  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Shopping cart session cookie | oscsid | Yes | This cookie is used to track your session so you can place an order. It is deleted when you close your browser. | Low |   
Anonymous user information cookie | ic_a | Yes | This cookie stores an id link to information such as if you have decided to view prices including or excluding VAT and the products you have recently viewed. The cookie file itself contains no personally identifiable information. | Low |   
Registered user information cookie | ic_p | Yes | This cookie stores an id link to information to enable users who have previously registered with us to log in and place orders. If you do not register with our site, this cookie will not be used. The cookie file itself contains no personally identifiable information. | Low |   
Google Analytics | __utma  
__utmb  
__utmc  
__utmx  
__utmxx  
__utmz | No | These cookies are used to help us track aggregate usage of our website. These cookies pass data in an anonymous form. | Low | [Click here](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)  
ClickTale | WRIgnore  
WRUID | No | ClickTale is a service that allows us to collect data about how users use our site. We use this data to help improve our website and the experience for our customers. | Low | [Click here](http://www.clicktale.com/privacy_service.aspx)  
Crazy Egg | is_returning | No | Crazy Egg is a service that allows us to see in aggregate form where users click and interact with our website. All data is collected in an anonymous form. | Low | [Click here](http://www.crazyegg.com/privacy)  
Criteo | Third-party cookies only | No | Criteo is a retargeting service which uses cookies to target banner advertisements, based on the products you view on our site. Although no first-party cookies are used, third-party cookies from Criteo may be saved on your system while browsing our site. You can opt out of all Criteo cookie use by clicking the more information link. | Medium | [Click here](http://www.criteo.com/en/privacy-policy)  
  
#### Changes to this privacy policy

Any future changes to this privacy policy will be updated as soon as possible on this page.

#### More information

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, you can contact us at any time. [Click here to contact us](https://www.clothes2order.ie/contact.php).
